Who's a handsome boy?
Come on, Solomon! Come on, baby!
Over here!
Woo!
Hey!
Solomon!
You hear me?
Come on, Solomon! Come on, baby!
Hey, do you want something to drink?
I don't drink.
Well, not even water?
Do you have any idea what they put in water?
Over here!
Woo!
Hey, good boy! Good Solomon! Good Solomon! Good boy! Good boy!
Who's a good boy? Who's a good boy?
Keep working! Hurry up!
I can only get a detention for so long!
High boy! High boy!
Fix it!
I ought to work in silence!
Oh! Oh!
Sheep-fart!
Stop it!
No! No!
Wait!
Solomon!
Solomon! Come here! Come here!
Come here! Oh, God!
Don't turn around!
They don't want me!
I am filled with scotch and bitterness and impure thoughts!
I can hear ferris right now! For cream!
Got it!
Afternoon, Solomon!
I'm sorry!
Hey, mister! Everybody says you're a dick.
I don't know what that means, but I don't believe it.
I don't think it's gonna work.
But good luck.
Yeah!
Hey, listen.
I want to see you here opening day.
I don't fraternize, Mr. Me.
I'm sure I'll have plenty of reports.
We can open.